The first time my mom saw jackfruit hanging from a tree,
she was amazed, just like a three-year-old child.
She didn’t touch a single vegetable in the pot.
I tried to smooth things over, saying it was just her playful humor.
But on the way home, my father said to me,
This is the ending he traded for—
after giving me decades of his best years.
My father…...
has never lost his innocence and curiosity toward the world.
But because of me,
he put on the weight of another small home.
How long has it been since you last hugged your father?
she thought the dipping sauce was tomato soup made by the waiter.
When we had hotpot,
She obediently finished the entire bowl of “sauce.”
“I must have embarrassed you.”
“I’m sorry.”